shiprocket.in 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy | ShipRocket.in

ShipRocketTM collects e-mail addresses and other contact details of people who register at our website and send us e-mail. The information we collect is not shared with or sold to others except under the certain circumstances and which your use of the Service is deemed to provide to us a valid consent to disclose the following: In order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ShipRocket’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

We share information about our Members with third parties, such as advertisers or partners, for marketing and promotional purposes. However, except as otherwise ShipRocket does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other companies. ShipRocket uses your information on a cumulative basis to help operate our web sites and enhance our web sites design, improve our content, our services and usability. We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the web site, new Services, and special offers. We always use a secure connection when collecting personal financial information from you. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

Your ShipRocket account is password-protected and you are free to create further users and user groups to whom you shall assign Usernames and Passwords, so only you and those you designate can access it and view the member information relevant to your account. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. ShipRocket reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our homepage so that you are aware of what information we collect. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

#### ShipRocket App Privacy Policy

KartRocket and ShipRocket built the ShipRocket-Ecommerce Logistics Solutions – COD app as a free app. This SERVICE is provided by KartRocket and Shiprocket at no cost and is intended for use as is. This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.

If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at ShipRocket – Ecommerce Logistics Solutions – COD, unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

For a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to e.g. users name, address, location, mobile number etc. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you. We you Google Anaytics to track usage.

**Log Data**

We want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your devices’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, configuration of the app when utilising our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your devices’s internal memory. This Services does not uses these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collection information and to improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

**Service Providers**

We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

  * To facilitate our Service;
  * To provide the Service on our behalf;
  * To perform Service-related services; or
  * To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

**Security**

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Links to Other Sites**  
This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

**Children’s Privacy**

These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. [I|We] do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case [I|we] discover that a child under 13 has provided [me|us] with personal information, [I|we] immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact [me|us] so that [I|we] will be able to do necessary actions.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
